Oleksandr Buhai

 $\frac{368-299-7666 \mid \underline{oleksandr.buugay@gmail.com} \mid \underline{https://www.linkedin.com/in/alex-buhai-95a35227b} \\ \underline{https://github.com/OleksandrBuhai}$

Summary

Experienced front end developer with a professional background in crafting complex, interactive web projects since 2021. High at cross-browser development, web standards, usability, responsive web development, and application architecture. I enjoy creating products that will benefit people in the future.

EDUCATION

IT-Incubator.io

Front-End Developer May 2020 – May 2021

NTUU KPI

Studied Manufacturing Engineering

Aug. 2015 – May 2019

IPTKisSUMDU

College Degree in Manufacturing Technology

May 2013 – May 2015

EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer Apr 2023 - Jul 2023

Berlin Labs LLC Remote

• Developing new user-facing features using React

• Participation in the development of a project for the sale of photo \ video.

• Optimizing components for maximum performance

• Building reusable components

Front-End Developer

Self employ

Development of landing pages;Developing features to enhance the user experience

• Optimizing web pages for maximum speed and scalability.

• Ensuring web design is optimized for smartphones

• Fix Bugs

Škoda Auto

Production Supervisor

Addressing technical challenges

• Managed both equipment and a team, ensuring smooth operations and quality standards

• Addressing technical challenges

Graphic Assistant Dec 2016 – Jul 2017

Mindy Support

• Data Processing for Neural Networks

• Image Processing for Future Use

Projects

Portfolio | React, JavaScript, CSS

- https://oleksandrbuhai.github.io/Portfolio/
- Working with libraries framer-motion , React styled component, tsparticles

Technical Skills

Lanuages: English, Czech, Ukranian

ProgLanguages: JavaScript, TypeScript HTML/CSS

Frameworks: React, Redux, Redux Toolkit, Tailwind CSS, jQuery, Material-UI

Developer Tools: Git, Visual Studio Code, IntelliJ

Kyiv, Ukraine

Kviv. Ukraine

Konotop, Ukraine

Jun 2022 - Mar 2023

May 2019 - Dec 2021

Mladá Boleslav, CZ

Mladá Boleslav, CZ